<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bike Safety</string>
    <string name="introHeading"><u>Welcome</u></string>
    <string name="introBodyText1">\tIn today’s time, biking is becoming a more common means of transportation than ever before.
        The number of bikers has grown significantly within the past few years: between 2000 and 2009, the number of regular bike
        commuters increased by 70% across the United States.
    </string>
     <string name="introBodyText2">\tHowever, it is important not to rush into the stream of all the bikers
        around you before considering your safety. Biking can be just as safe as driving as long as you follow the laws and
        apply common sense. Here are 5 tips which should put you along the right path to a safe ride.
     </string>
    <!--<string name="title_slide1">Slide 1</string>-->
    <string name="fact1_header">General Rules of the Road</string>
    <string name="fact1_body">\tGeneral rules of the road from vehicular driving also apply to bicycles. They are considered road vehicles just like
        cars and trucks. Therefore, be sure to always: stop at a red light, stay within your lane, make a complete stop at stop signs, etc.
    </string>
    <string name="fact2_header">Always Wear a Helmet!</string>
    <string name="fact2_body">\tThis should be blatantly obvious: always wear a helmet! When you first place the helmet on without snapping in the
        straps, it should wiggle with minimal movement when you shake your head. There should be two finger widths of space between your eyebrows
        and helmet. Once you snap on the straps, they should form a Y-shape just below your ears. The helmet should feel comfortable yet snug.
    </string>
    <string name="fact3_header">Passing from the Left</string>
    <string name="fact3_body">\tWhenever passing a vehicle, always pass on the left (driver side). This prevents you from placing yourself inside
        of the driver’s blind spot. Instead, you’re more likely to be within their field of view.
    </string>
</resources>
