<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bike Safety</string>
    <string name="introHeading"><u>Welcome</u></string>
    <string name="introBodyText1">\tIn today’s time, biking is becoming a more common means of transportation than ever before.
        The number of bikers has grown significantly within the past few years: between 2000 and 2009, the number of regular bike
        commuters increased by 70% across the United States.
    </string>
     <string name="introBodyText2">\tHowever, it is important not to rush into the stream of all the bikers
        around you before considering your safety. Biking can be just as safe as driving as long as you follow the laws and
        apply common sense. Here are 5 tips which should put you along the right path to a safe ride.
     </string>
    <!--<string name="title_slide1">Slide 1</string>-->
    <string name="fact1_header">General Rules of the Road</string>
    <string name="fact1_body">\tGeneral rules of the road from vehicular driving also apply to bicycles. They are considered road vehicles just like
        cars and trucks. Therefore, be sure to always: stop at a red light, stay within your lane, make a complete stop at stop signs, etc.
    </string>
    <string name="fact2_header">Always Wear a Helmet!</string>
    <string name="fact2_body">\tThis should be blatantly obvious: always wear a helmet! When you first place the helmet on without snapping in the
        straps, it should wiggle with minimal movement when you shake your head. There should be two finger widths of space between your eyebrows
        and helmet. Once you snap on the straps, they should form a Y-shape just below your ears. The helmet should feel comfortable yet snug.
    </string>
    <string name="fact3_header">Passing from the Left</string>
    <string name="fact3_body">\tWhenever passing a vehicle, always pass on the left (driver side). This prevents you from placing yourself inside
        of the driver’s blind spot. Instead, you’re more likely to be within their field of view.
    </string>
    <string name="fact4_header">Changing Lanes</string>
    <string name="fact4_body">\tIf you are about to change into a different lane, be sure to look behind you before doing so. While looking back,
        try your best to continuing biking in a straight line. The combination of looking back and biking straight is a technique that is sometimes
        known as “scanning”.
    </string>
    <string name="fact5_header">Lane Usage</string>
    <string name="fact5_body">\tBe sure to properly place yourself in a lane. If a bike lane is available, use it! Your community designed them to
        keep bikers such as yourself away from harms away. Otherwise, the law in most states is for bikers to stay as far to the right as possible.
        However, if the road is particularly narrow, do not be afraid to use the entire lane. Your safety is a higher priority than the convenience
        of vehicular drivers.
    </string>
    <string name="reference1"><a href="http://bicyclesafe.com/index.html">Michael Bluejay’s Guide</a>: Great guide for avoiding being hit in various
        situations. Also provides notable advice in general.
    </string>
    <string name="reference2"><a href="http://bikeleague.org/content/rules-road-0">The League of American Bicyclists</a>: Their information is a bit vague
        but their videos and other resources (classes and biking guides) are useful.
    </string>
    <string name="reference3"><a href="http://greatist.com/fitness/bicycle-safety-101">Article by Sophia Breene</a>: More helpful information. Check out if
        you live in the best (or worst :/) cities for biking!
    </string>
    <string name="reference4"><a href="http://www.nhtsa.gov/people/injury/pedbimot/bike/kidsandbikesafetyweb/">National HIghway Traffic Safety Administration</a>:
        Additional safety information provided by the NHTSA.
    </string>
</resources>
